/*const myQuestions = 
[
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62373588cfe13103f55eb53f",
        "correctAnswer": "Montenegro",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Yemen",
            "Mexico",
            "Monaco"
        ],
        "question": "Which region of the world uses '.me' at the end of its web addresses?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "id": "62399eccaf96521963a08708",
        "correctAnswer": "Germany",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Spain",
            "Italy",
            "Argentina"
        ],
        "question": "Which country won the 2014 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Brazil?",
        "tags": [
            "football",
            "soccer",
            "world_cup"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd6c",
        "correctAnswer": "Fatboy Slim",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Basement Jaxx",
            "Chemical Brothers",
            "Daft Punk"
        ],
        "question": "Whose Albums Include \"Better Living By Chemistry\" & \"You've Come A Long Way Baby\"?",
        "tags": [
            "music_albums"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "625064d0e12f6dec240bdfcf",
        "correctAnswer": "Eddy Grant",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Devo",
            "Suzi Quatro",
            "Nick Gilder"
        ],
        "question": "'Electric Avenue' was a one hit wonder in 1983 by which artist?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "one_hit_wonders"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd88",
        "correctAnswer": "Jenny",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Brenda",
            "Lisa",
            "Julie"
        ],
        "question": "Who Is Tommy Tutone Trying To Call When He Dials \"867 5309\"",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcea",
        "correctAnswer": "Indo-European",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Niger–Congo",
            "Dravidian",
            "Kra–Dai"
        ],
        "question": "The language 'Russian' belongs to which language family?",
        "tags": [
            "language"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950baa",
        "correctAnswer": "Nine Inch Nails",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "In This Moment",
            "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band",
            "Animal Collective"
        ],
        "question": "Which American industrial rock band released the studio album 'The Downward Spiral'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500d8",
        "correctAnswer": "Leeds United",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Chelsea",
            "Newcastle United",
            "Everton"
        ],
        "question": "A Statue Of Billy Bremner Stands Outside The Ground Of Which Football Ground?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Film & TV",
        "id": "624dba44de6018633d31f6bc",
        "correctAnswer": "Carly Simon",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Lulu",
            "Nancy Sinatra",
            "Matt Monro"
        ],
        "question": "Who performed the theme song to the James Bond film The Spy Who Loved Me?",
        "tags": [
            "james_bond",
            "film",
            "soundtracks"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c6e",
        "correctAnswer": "The Shepherds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Three Wise Men",
            "King Herod",
            "The Stable Boy"
        ],
        "question": "According to the bible, who were the baby Jesus's first visitors?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    }
]
*/



fetch("string representing a URL to a data source")
.then(function(response) {
  return response.json();
})
.then(function(json){
  // Use this data inside of `json` to do DOM manipulation
})

fetch("string representing a URL to a data source")
  /*
    The function above returns an object that represents what the data source
    sent back. It does *not* return the actual content.

    We have to call the then() method on the object that comes back. then()
    takes as its argument a function that receives the response as its argument.
    Inside of the function, we do whatever processing we need, but at the end we
    *have to return* the content that we've gotten out of the response.

    The response has some basic functions on it for the most common data types.
    The most important ones are .json() and .text().

    This callback function is usually only one line: returning the content from
    the response. What we return from this function will be used in the _next_
    then() function.
  */

  .then(function(response) {
    return response.json();
  })

  /*
    The function above returns the content from the response.
    We can use that content inside of the callback function that's
    passed in to the then() function below.
  */

  .then(function(json){
    // Use this data inside of `json` to do DOM manipulation
  })

  fetch('http://api.open-notify.org/astros.json')
.then(function(response) {
  return response.json();
})
.then(function(json) {
  console.log(json)
});


fetch('db.json').then(function (response){
  return response.json();
}).then(function (obj){
  console.log(obj);
}).catch(function(error){
  console.error('Something Went Wrong!');
  sonsole.error(error);
});


//getting the data from API


async function getQuestion(){
  const response = await fetch(api_url);
  const data = await response.json();
  console.log(data);
};

Json Server Video:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NM4gB8J1uF4







<form class="form-inline" action="/action_page.php">
  <label for="FullName">Full Name:</label>
  <input type="FullName" id="FullName" placeholder="Enter Full Name" name="FullName">
  <label for="Mobile">Mobile:</label>
  <input type="MobileNumber" id="MobileNumber" placeholder="Enter Mobile Number" name="MobileNumber">
  <label for="totalScore">Total Score:</label>
  <input type="totalScore" id="totalScore" placeholder="Total Score" name="totalScore">
  <button id="dataSubmit">Submit</button>
</form>

.form-inline label {
	margin: 5px 10px 5px 5px;
	font-size: large;
	color: red;
  }
  
  .form-inline input {
	vertical-align: middle;
	margin: 5px 10px 5px 6px;
	padding: 20px;
	background-color: #fff;
	border: 1px solid #ddd;
	font-size: large;
	color: red
  }
